articlegold.com 2012-11-01

# Privacy Policy - Articlegold.com

_Amended: 19-Mar-2011_

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

## What information do we collect?

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:

  * information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views);
  * information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services
  * information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us;
  * information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our website services, email notifications and/or newsletters
  * any other information that you choose to send to us;

## Cookies

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We use cookies on this website. A cookie is a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We use session cookies to keep track of you whilst you navigate the website; and persistent cookies to enable our website to recognise you when you visit. Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.

Articlegold.com uses Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information.

Articlegold.com uses reputable services like Google Adsense (www.google.com/adsense) to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, these companies may use cookies to collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information, consult the privacy policy of Google at http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy/ .

* The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on the websites of its partners, such as websites displaying AdSense ads or participating in Google certified ad networks. When users visit a partner's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help better serve and manage ads on the publisher's site(s) and across the web.

* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).)

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking "Tools", "Internet Options", "Privacy", and selecting "Block all cookies" using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.

## Using your personal data

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

### We may use your personal information to:

  * administer the website;
  * improve your browsing experience by personalising the website;
  * enable your use of the services available on the website;
  * send to you goods purchased via the website, and supply to you services purchased via the website;
  * send statements and invoices to you, and collect payments from you;
  * send you general (non-marketing) commercial communications;
  * send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;
  * send to you our newsletter and other marketing communications relating to our business which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications by emailing contact @ articlegold.com)
  * deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to the website;

We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.

## Disclosures

We may disclose information about you to insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes as set out in this privacy policy.

### In addition, we may disclose information about you:

  * to the extent that we are required to do so by law;
  * in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;
  * in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk);

Except as provided in this privacy policy, we will not provide your information to third parties.

## International data transfers

Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

If you are in the European Economic Area (EEA), information which you provide may be transferred to countries which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the EEA.

You expressly agree to such transfers of personal information.

## Security of your personal data

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

You are responsible for keeping your password and user details confidential.

## Policy amendments

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

## Your rights

You may instruct us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes by email to contact @ articlegold.com at any time. (In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal data for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt-out of the use of your personal data for marketing purposes.)

## Third party websites

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites.

## Updating information

Please let us know if the personal information which we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated.

## Contact us

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to contact @ articlegold.com or by post to;

ArticleGold.com Service,  
Xenyo Limited,  
1/F 154 Tai Po Tsai Vil.,  
Clear Water Bay Road, Hong Kong.
